<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Advent of Code on Kaitlin Maciejewski</title>
    <link>https://k-maciejewski.github.io/advent-of-code/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Advent of Code on Kaitlin Maciejewski</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://k-maciejewski.github.io/advent-of-code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://k-maciejewski.github.io/advent-of-code/posts/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://k-maciejewski.github.io/advent-of-code/posts/readme/</guid>
      <description>Advent-of-Code-2021 About my method to read in descriptions and data for Advent of Code 2021
(Using R)
library(rvest)
library(httr)
1. Read the description for part 1, where N is the day number
`r read_html(&amp;quot;https://adventofcode.com/2021/day/N&amp;quot;) %&amp;gt;% html_element(&amp;quot;.day-desc&amp;quot;) %&amp;gt;% paste(collapse = &#39;\n&#39;) `  2. To load data file, you need your cookie information
Login with OAuth, then find your cookie information. (Ex: inspect element &amp;gt; network &amp;gt; input (may need to refresh) &amp;gt; scroll to cookies)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2021: Day 1</title>
      <link>https://k-maciejewski.github.io/advent-of-code/posts/aoc2021_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://k-maciejewski.github.io/advent-of-code/posts/aoc2021_1/</guid>
      <description>— Day 1: Sonar Sweep —   You’re minding your own business on a ship at sea when the overboard alarm goes off! You rush to see if you can help. Apparently, one of the Elves tripped and accidentally sent the sleigh keys flying into the ocean!  Before you know it, you’re inside a submarine the Elves keep ready for situations like this. It’s covered in Christmas lights (because of course it is), and it even has an experimental antenna that should be able to track the keys if you can boost its signal strength high enough; there’s a little meter that indicates the antenna’s signal strength by displaying 0-50 stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2021: Day 2</title>
      <link>https://k-maciejewski.github.io/advent-of-code/posts/aoc2021_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://k-maciejewski.github.io/advent-of-code/posts/aoc2021_2/</guid>
      <description>— Day 2: Dive! —   Now, you need to figure out how to pilot this thing.  It seems like the submarine can take a series of commands like forward 1, down 2, or up 3:   forward X increases the horizontal position by X units.   down X increases the depth by X units.   up X decreases the depth by X units.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2021: Day 3</title>
      <link>https://k-maciejewski.github.io/advent-of-code/posts/aoc2021_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://k-maciejewski.github.io/advent-of-code/posts/aoc2021_3/</guid>
      <description>— Day 3: Binary Diagnostic —   The submarine has been making some odd creaking noises, so you ask it to produce a diagnostic report just in case.  The diagnostic report (your puzzle input) consists of a list of binary numbers which, when decoded properly, can tell you many useful things about the conditions of the submarine. The first parameter to check is the power consumption.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
